Now that the training job is completed,
训练作业创建完毕后
we can build the SageMaker model.
下面构建 SageMaker 模型
Remember, the SageMaker model is really a collection of
SageMaker 模型其实就是一个信息集合
information that includes both a link to the model artifacts,
其中包含模型工件的链接
that is the saved files that were created by our training job,
模型工件是指在训练作业中保存的文件
and some information that describes how those model artifacts should be used.
以及描述应该如何使用模型工件的其他信息
Before we do that however,
在创建模型之前
let's actually take a look at the training job inside of the SageMaker console.
我们先在 SageMaker 控制台中看看训练作业
To do that, let's open up the tab that currently is on the S3 console.
打开目前位于 S3 控制台上的标签页
If I click on the icon in the top left corner,
点击左上角的图标
it brings me to the main AWS console,
转到主 AWS 控制台
and from here, we can choose whichever service we want to look at.
我们可以从这里选择任何服务
In our case, we want to scroll down to Machine Learning and
向下滚动到“Machine Learning”部分
select "Amazon" SageMaker to open up the SageMaker console.
选择“Amazon SageMaker”以打开 SageMaker 控制台
Now, the last time we were here,
上次访问 AWS 控制台时
we clicked on "Notebook instances" which
我们点击了“Notebook instances”
shows each of the notebook instances that we have created.
它会显示我们创建的所有 notebook 实例
This time, we want to take a look at "Training jobs."
这次 我们将查看“Training jobs”
As you can see how I have quite a lot of training jobs that
可以看到 我在使用 SageMaker 时
I have built up over my time playing with SageMaker.
构建了很多个训练作业
However, this one right here at the top
最上面的这个训练作业
corresponds to the training job that we just completed in the low-level notebook.
就是我们刚刚在低阶 notebook 中完成的训练作业
How do I know this?
我是如何判断的？
Well, for two reasons.
原因有两个
First, the creation time is today,
首先 创建时间是今天
and secondly, when we named this training job,
其次 当我们命名该训练作业时
remember we included a timestamp at the end of it,
我们在末尾添加了时间戳
which again includes today's date,
也包含今天的日期
and the time that I created this training job.
即我创建此训练作业的时间
If I select this and click on it,
选择并点击该作业后
it shows me some information about the training job.
可以看到关于该作业的一些信息
One piece of information that may be of use to you in
有一条信息以后对你可能有用
the future is down at the bottom where it says "View logs."
在底部有个“View logs”
If you click on this,
点击“View logs”
it will open up a,
将打开一个
CloudWatch dashboard, from which you can take a look
CloudWatch 信息中心
at the output that was created by that training job.
你可以在此处查看训练作业创建的输出
So, if you have any errors that show up while training,
如果在训练过程中出现任何错误
they will appear here.
这些错误将出现在这里
This can be very useful tool when you are
当你创建比这个作业
working on creating jobs that are a little more complicated than this one.
更加复杂的作业时 这些信息将很有用
Going back to the low-level notebook,
回到低阶 notebook
again our training job has completed, so,
训练作业已运行完毕
now it's time to build the model inside of SageMaker.
现在开始在 SageMaker 中构建模型
So, how do we do that?
如何构建？
Well, as I said before,
正如我之前提到的
a model in SageMaker is really a collection of data.
SageMaker 中的模型是一个数据集合
In particular, it includes a link to
它包含模型工件的链接
the model artifacts which we can extract from the training job information,
我们可以从训练作业中获取模型工件
and some additional information about how those model artifacts can be used.
还包含关于如何使用这些模型工件的其他信息
Now, just like when we created a training job,
就像创建训练作业一样
a model must have a name that is unique.
模型必须具有唯一名称
So, the way we are going to create the model name here is to take the training job name,
我们可以使用训练作业名称
which was already unique because it had a timestamp,
因为训练作业有时间戳 已经是唯一名称
and append model to it.
然后在后面加上 -model
Once we have the model name,
设置好模型名称后
we package up information including a link to
打包信息
the model artifacts and a link to the docker container,
包括模型工件的链接以及 docker 容器的链接
which contains the algorithm necessary to perform
docker 容器中包含
inference using our creative model artifacts.
使用创建的模型工件进行推理所必需的算法
Lastly, we use SageMaker object to
最后 使用 SageMaker 对象创建模型
create a model which includes the name that we specified,
传入指定的名称
a role in the data structure which
角色以及数据结构
includes a link to the container and a link to the model artifacts.
其中包含容器的链接和模型工件的链接
So, now that we've run this cell, what actually happened?
如果运行此单元格 会发生什么？
Well, if we go back to the SageMaker dashboard,
回到 SageMaker 信息中心
on the left hand side,
在左侧
if we click on models,
点击“Models”
again I have a whole bunch here built up from previous experiments with SageMaker.
这里列出了我使用 SageMaker 实验的各种模型
If we look at this top one here,
看看顶部的模型
it looks like the name of
这个名称
the training job that recreated including the correct timestamp,
由包含时间戳的训练作业名称
with the word model upended.
以及 -model 组成
So, this is the model that we just created in the notebook.
这就是我们刚刚在 notebook 中创建的模型
If I click on here,
点击该模型
notice that all of the information we provided is now included.
发现我们提供的所有信息都列在了此页面
Looking through, we can see a link to
可以看到模型工件的链接
the model artifacts and a location of the inference code.
以及推理代码的位置